familyhealthandhome.com 2011-05-16

# Privacy Policy : Family Health and Home

**Privacy Policy for familyhealthandhome.com**

With Privacy becoming such a very sensitive issue on the internet today, and I understand how much all of you value security and privacy. I am committed to safeguarding your privacy while you are visiting ite http://familyhealthandhome.com

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for familyhealthandhome.com  
**  
Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, I use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. My site use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, I have no access to or control over these cookies, once I have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.

Google, one of our third-party advertisers who have running ads on http://familyhealthandhome.com/, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. I encourage my users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
I use outside ad companies to display ads on my site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. Please check their website for respective privacy policy.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the privacy policy of my website, http://familyhealthandhome.com, please contact me through the contact form on this website, and address it to me, [Basti](http://familyhealthandhome.com/2008/11/basti/ "Basti") Dizon, with “Privacy Policy” on the subject.
